Guide to the Zelda Fichandler papers, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Zelda Fichandler papers
  - correspondence: prospective European tour, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: future tours, mid 1980's (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: 1983-1984 prospects (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - misc. training information (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - misc. training information (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - misc. training information (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - misc. theater information (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - A Traveling Jewish Theatre, information (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Trinity Players, information (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Trinity Rep. Company, information (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Trud (Soviet Paper) information (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - George Tsypin, misc information (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Trump Shuttle account book (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: George Udvarhelyi (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: George Udvarhelyi (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - USIA, misc info (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - University Resident Theatre (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Irene Vacchina (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - info: Lev Vainshtein (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - information, Russell Vanderbrouche (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - correspondence, Variety magazine (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Miriam L. Varon (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: John Patrick Vincent (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - correspondence and info: Marty Vinograd (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Viscalia, CA theatre conference (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: David Visser (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - correspondence and info: Arthur Wagner (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - speech by David Wade on HR 4545 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - info ono Nina Varonel (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - WAMU 88.5 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Howard Walberg (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Ted Walch (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Joseph Walker (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Wallace Funds (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - The Wall St. Journal (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Barbara Walton (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Pale Wasserman (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Ruth Webb (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - WETA interviews, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - "The Secret Place", information (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: Kate Weber (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - correspondence: Carl Weber (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - WETA: Zelda's fundraising statement (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - WGMS award 1987 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - correspondence: Susan White (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - misc invitations to the White House (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - correspondence: Robert Whitehead (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Whole Theatre Co (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - correspondence: Denise Weil (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - barbara Weisburger (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Sue Weil (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - 3 reel to reel videos (Box 26, Folder 34)
    Loose in box.
  - correspondence: Mary Dolan (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - a script in Russian and two maps of tennessee (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - misc. materials, ITP 2-3 One Act Plays (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - misc. materials, ITP 2-3 One Act Plays (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "Inner City", playbill (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "The Inner Journey", press release (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - "Inner Voices", playbill (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - misc. materials, ITP 2-3 One Act Plays (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "Insignificance", script, notes and misc. materials (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - "The Importance of being Ernest", playbill and notes (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - misc. materials, ITP 2-3 One Act Plays (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Monsieur de Moliere", notes (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - "The Impresario", playbill (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - "The Importance of Being Ernest", playbill and notes (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Howard Rosenstone (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - misc. materials, ITP 2-3 One Act Plays (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - audio tapes, "Inherit the Wind" (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Large audio cassette case.
  - Harry Weese - John Corley (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Elie Wiezel (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Richard Wilbur, NEA event (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Ron White (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Harry Weese (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Thornton Wilder (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Jackie Eric-Williams (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - news clippings on Tennessee Williams (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - info on the Williamstown Festival (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - info, the Wilma Theatre (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Wilson College (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - remarks by Zelda on Ms. Halo Wines (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - clipping on Bill Wingate (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Janelle Winston (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - correspondence :Howard Witt (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Dr. Martin Wolfe (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: The Womens Center of Northern Virginia (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - brochures from seasons past (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - womens playwright conference: 1988 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - women ini film and video (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - "The Inspector General", playbill and correspondence (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - misc. correspondence 1966-1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - "In the Well of the House", playbill (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - "In Two Keys", playblill (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - American Conservatory Theatre press releases, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - script cards and notes for "The Great Monekey Trial" (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - "Inherit the Wind", playbill, script with notes (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - "Inherit the Wind:, script with notes cont. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - notes on the Scopes Monkey Trial (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - misc. playbills for "Inherit the Wind" (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - misc. info on Russian Tour (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - misc. correspondence, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - misc. information, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - stage mamagers daily reports for "Inherit the Wind", 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - misc. info and notes for "Inherit the Wind", 1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - misc. info and notes for "Inherit the Wind", 1973 (cont.) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - publicity brochure for "Inherit the Wind" (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - "Herringbone", playbill (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "The Heros of Xochiquipa", script (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - "The Heros of Xochiquipa", script (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - NY Times clipping for 1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - correspondence on "Hidden River" (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - "Highest Standard of Living", playbill (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - notes and correspondence on "The High Heeled Women" (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - review of "Hijinks" (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - "Him", correspondence, notes and reviews (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - "History of American Film", correspondence, notes, performance reports and sales records (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - playbill/brochure for "Henry IV, Henry V and Richard II" (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - "The History of American Film", script, reviews and notes (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - "Hitchen", script (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - "Hold Me", notes (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - "Home", playbill, correspondence (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - "The Homecoming", playbill and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - "Home", script, playbill, notes and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - "Hope of the Heart", playbill (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - "Horatio", playbill, stage managers daily reports and box office reports (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - "Hosanna", correspondence (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - "The Hostage", playbills, notes and misc. production info. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - "Hot House", artical (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - "Hot House", notes (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - "The Hot L Baltimore", playbills, reviews and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - "Hough in Blazes", playbill (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - "The House of Bernard Alba", playbill/program (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - "The House of Blue Leaves", playbills and production information (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - "How Do You Do", misc. info. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - "How I Got That Storey", review (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - "How it All Began", playbill (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - "How the other Half loves", playbill, notes, reviews (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - "Hughie", artical/review (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - "The Human Comedy", playbill (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - "Hunger and Thirst", correspondence (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - "Hunting Cockroaches", misc. info (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - "Hurly Burly", playbill (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - "I am a Woman", script (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - "I am a Woman", playbills, notes, reviews (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - "Ice", background information (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - "The Iceman Cometh", playbill (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - "The Ice Age", playbill, reviews, notes, etc. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - "Idiot's Delight", production information (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - "I Got a Song", script and correspondence (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - "The IK", playbills and reviews (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - "I'm Getting my Act togethor and taking it on the Road", playbill (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - "The Invalide", playbill, production notes (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - "The Immigrant", production material (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - financail situation of Arena Stage and Theatre in general (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - articals on theatre (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - info on "Importance of the Arts" (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - research for testimony on NEA budget (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Arena Stage's annual reports, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - articals on black theatre and minorities (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - bills from Century Lighting for new building (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - insurance for the New Building (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Lighting catalogues and information (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building,and Lighting catalogues and information. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, Sound (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, seating (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - misc. maintinance manuels for new equipment (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - correspondence with engineers about new building, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - correspondence with Land Redevelopment Agency (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - correspondence with Land Redevelopment Agency (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - information on folding walls for new building (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - blue prints for Lobby Lighting with costs (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - insurance information for the new building (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - misc. correspondence regarding Arena Stage (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - misc. correspondence regarding Arena Stage (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Information on sound equipment for new Building (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - bids from contractors to construct new building (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - invoices and correspondence for electrical and lighting for the new building (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - blue prints and correspondence about acoustics for the new building (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - building acoustics cont. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - "A Raisin in the Sun", stage managers weekly reports, perfromance reports, rehersal sch. and misc. information (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - pre-production info for "Raisin in the Sun" (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - "Maybe I'm Doing it Wrong", playbills and reviews (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - "Rat in the Skull", playbills (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - "Raw Youth", playbill (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - "Real Estate", playbill, production notes, stage managers reports, research and reviews (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - "The Real Inspector Hound", playbill and contract info (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - "Rebel Women", playbill (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - correspondence regarding "A Recent Killing" (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - "The Recruiting Officer", playbill (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - correspondence regarding "Red Cross", "Muzeeka" (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - "Red Rover, Red Rover", correspondence (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - "The Regard of Flight", reviews (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - 'The Rehersal", correspondence (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - "Relatively Speaking", production meeting notes and correspondence (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - "The Removalists", correspondence (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - "Request Concerts", playbill (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - "Requiem for a Heavyweight", playbill (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - "Restoration", production notes and misc. materials (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - "Arturo Ui", correspondence (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - "The Revengers Tragedy", script w/production notes (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - "Richard II", playbill (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - "Richard's Cork Leg", correspondence (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - "A Rich Full Life", playlab (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - "Ride a Cock Horse", correspondence (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - "Ride Across Lake Constance", playbill (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - "Right you Are (if you think so)", playbills (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - "Ring Around the Moon", opening remarks and misc. items (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - "The Rivals", playbill (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - "The River and Ravines", correspondence (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - "The Negro Ensamble Company", playbill (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - "The Road", artical and review (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - "The Road to Mecca", review (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - "Rocket to the Moon", program (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - "Romance in Hard Times", review (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - "Romance Language", playbill (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - "Romeo and Juliet", character list (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - "A Room of Ones Own", playbill (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - "Room Service", playbills (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - "Rosenccrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead", playbill (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - "Rosemersholm" review (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - "The Rules of the Game", correspondence (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - "The Ruling Class", playbill and misc. materials (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - "Rum and Coke", playbill (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - "Runways", playbills (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - "The Runner Stumbles", playbills and reviews (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - "RUR", press release (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - "RUT", correspondence (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - "St. Carmen of the Main", review (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - "Saints Day", playbill and review (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - "St. Joan of the Stockyards", correspondence (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - "Salonika", playbill (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - "Saturday, Sunday, Monday", misc. information (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - "Saturday, Sunday, Monday", script (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - "Raisin", Playbill, Misc. production notes (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - "Raisin", Script (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - "Raisin", Playbills, Misc. production notes, Reviews and articles (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - "Rain", Playbill (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - "The Rabbit Foot", Invitation to Crossroads Theater, Playbills, Reviews and articles (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "Quilters", Playbill (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - "The Queen and the Rebels", Copy request (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - "Quatermaine's Terms", Playbills, Misc. production notes, reviews and articles (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - "Quantrill in Laurence", Correspondence with author (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - "Pygmalion", Playbill, Misc. production notes, Reviews and articles (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - "Purlie", Playbill (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All", Misc. production notes, stage notes, correspondence (Box 44, Folder 12)
    This was a seminar class Fichlander taught at Boston University.
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All", Extensive production notes, Production schedule (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All", Script (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Handwritten notes in margins
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All", Scripts, Correspondence, Misc. production notes. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    One script is in the original German.
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All", Playbill, Bibliography and Bio of the author (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All", Misc. production notes, Correspondence, Playbill (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick of it All", Misc. production notes, Playbill, Reviews and articles (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - "The Public", Correspondence, Review (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - "Prayer for my Daughter", Playbill (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - "The Price of Admission", Script (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - "The Price", Reviews and articles (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - "The Primary English Class", Playbill, Correspondence, Reviews and articles (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - "The Prince of Hornburg", Playbill, Reviews and articles (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - "The Prince of Mandalore", Correspondence, Reviews (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - "A Private Affair", Review (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - "The Private Life of the Third Reich", Review (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - "Private Lives", Playbill, Review (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - "Project Immortality", Articles (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - "Promenade", Script, Playbill, Misc. production notes, Review (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - "Promenade, All!", Playbill (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - "Pueblo", Misc. production notes and correspondence, Playbills, Articles (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Drawings related to this folder in Box 46B
  - "Pueblo", Script, Misc. notes (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - "Porch", Playbill (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - "Porgy and Bess", Playbills (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - "The Portage to San Cristobal of A. H.", Review, Program, Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - "Portrait of a Planet", Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - "Pantagleize", Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - "Prague Spring", Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - "Pravda", Program, Reviews and articles (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - 30th anniversary special promotion (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Gloria and Charlie Carshon (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Leslie Cass (actor): information on drinking difficulties and memorial service (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Douglas Carter (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Catholic University (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Anne Cattaneo (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Kenneth Cavander (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - "The Cell", reviews (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Center for Applied Linguistics (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: David Chambers (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Robert Chapline and Rick Winter (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Chautaqua institute (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - research from Chekov (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Zelda's trip to Chicago, no date given (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Minneapolis Childrens Theatre Co. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - info on the Citizens Exchange Council (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - info on the Committe on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - correspondence and info on Chinese visit (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Ann Chodoff (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - information on healthcare options (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Richard Coe (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Alex Cohen (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Marcus Cohn (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: The College of the Fellows of the American Theatre (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Summer program at Colorado College, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - "Comedie Francaise", artical (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - colorado teaching information (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Colorado summer position 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Colorado, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Colorado Summer 1987 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Tom Cone (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Arts Caucus Educational Program (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Congressional Club donation to Arena Stage (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Colorado summer teaching 1985 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - contact information sheets (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - contact information sheets (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - contact information sheets (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Paul Cooke (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: David Copelin (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - letter of recommendation for Jennifer Corcoran (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Cornell University (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Cornerstone Theatre Co. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Roger Cornish (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Cosmopolitan Club - NYC (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - speech for Cosmo Club lecture (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Norman Cousins (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Rose Robison Cowen (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - map to Joan Andrews picnic (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Lucian Pintilie (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - plaque record (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - information on playlab 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - info: the playlab (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - playlab scene shop, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - playlab: The Sexes (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - info about playwrights (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - The Playwrights Center (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Poland (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Henry Popkin (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - clippings on post modernist theater (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Bob Potter (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Janey Pouse (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Harold Prince (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - production intern program (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - info on new production corrdinator (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Professional Older Women's Theatre (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Princess Grace Foundation (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Andrew Prosky (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - info on Robert Prosky, actor (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - info on John Prosky, actor (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - marketing director (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - publishers (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Sissy Pulley (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - correspondence and photo: Nancy Quinn (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Jose Quintero (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - "Lunin:Theatre of Death", playbill (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Margaret Ramsey (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Reagen budget cut articals (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Vanessa Redgrave (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Harry Reems (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - regional theatre articals (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: John Reich (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: John Reich (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - information on retreats (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - information on retreats (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - correspondence and info: Revson Foundation (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Stephen Richard (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Ron Ribman (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: David Richards (Box 52, Folder 5)